kingsera.com 2017-05-14

# Kingsera :: Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy of: TSIT Games (TSIT)

This is the Privacy Policy of TSIT Co, Hove, UK. It applies to all our websites and games operated by TSIT Co, or by its subsidiaries. (Kingsera.com, Kingsera.it, tadland.com, tsit.org, tsitgames.com)

TSIT shall handle all personal data which the user submits during the business relations strictly confidentially in compliance with all applicable data protection regulations. Details are provided in this Privacy Policy.

In the event that a link contained on the website operated by TSIT redirects the user to another website not operated by TSIT, TSIT draws the user's attention to the fact that the present Privacy Policy does not apply to this third-party website. TSIT is not responsible for how the operator of this website handles user data. In particular, TSIT is not responsible for the website not operated by TSIT not having same data protection standards as those that TSIT offers its users. TSIT recommends the user to carefully read the privacy policies of linked websites.

Which personal data does Kingsera collect, use and store?

TSIT collects, processes and stores the personal data which the user voluntarily submits to TSIT by electronic or other means of communication (e.g. in standard forms or otherwise on the websites and games operated by TSIT).

This includes data which the user provides to other users when communicating with them on the websites and games operated by TSIT.

In order to register for the use of the games operated by TSIT or in order to purchase a premium membership, the user must provide certain personal details, including his/her email address. If the user would like to purchase a premium membership for a user fee, this means that TSIT GAMES will require further information from the user, such as his/her postal address or credit card information. (If the user makes a payment by credit card or PayPal to any of our websites, we do not keep any card details as this is all done via a secure payment provider website or PayPal)

TSIT advises the user to handle their data carefully and sparingly, and consider what and with whom they would like to communicate via the websites and games operated by TSIT. Certain information, e.g. communications between users, is also visible for other users of the websites and games operated by TSIT.

Here are some examples of data stored by TSIT:

When a user accesses the websites and games operated by TSIT, TSIT automatically stores the domain name and/or the IP-address of the computer via which the user contacts TSIT, the date and the length of time spent on the websites and games operated by TSIT and the pages of the websites and games operated by Kingsera GAMES accessed by the user.

TSIT stores the user's email address. TSIT may use it to send newsletters and information on the games of TSIT to the user. The user may, of course, revoke his/her consent at any time in writing (e.g. by email) without incurring any costs, apart from the costs of transmitting the written revocation (at base rates). The user shall be given the opportunity in all information sent by TSIT and in every newsletter to refuse to accept further information and to dispatch an appropriate revocation.

What does TSIT do with the user's data?

TSIT collects, processes and stores the personal data of the user only insofar as Kingsera GAMES assumes that this reasonably serves legal business purposes. In other words: Kingsera GAMES collects, processes and stores the data of users so that TSIT can better understand the users of the websites and games operated by TSIT and thus offer them better services. For example, TSIT may not only use the stored data to directly process the licence agreement including all related possibilities of use (e.g. use of the games; participation in services related to the games; use of the services provided by customer support) but also in order to detect malfunctions or the abuse of websites and games operated by TSIT.

For this reason, TSIT will collect and store records which reflect how the websites and games operated by TSIT are used, e.g. in-game user activities and in-game communication between users or communication within game-related services. This includes the monitoring of playing patterns and checks for possible manipulations of game operations which can then serve to detect abusive or improper activities of users. TSIT uses special programs to detect infringements of the rules of the games, e.g. programs which can detect the use of unauthorised scripts and which can store the IP address and other data which the browser transfers as header information. Should TSIT discover that a user is acting in breach of his contractual obligations, e.g. by using unauthorised scripts, TSIT expressly reserves the right to merge the IP address of the respective user with other data which TSIT has on this user in order to bring the infringement to the attention of the user. TSIT might then take further steps against the respective user in order to restore regular game operations.

For the purpose of handling payments, TSIT has the right to disclose user data to service providers instructed to collect the user fee insofar as this is necessary for the calculation of the fee and for settlement with the user. Furthermore, TSIT is entitled to provide user data to third parties to whom receivables due to TSIT from the user have been assigned provided that this is necessary to collect the receivables. TSIT shall inform the user of the names of such third parties. If TSIT cooperates with third parties in order to provide its services, TSIT shall oblige such parties to comply with applicable data protection laws and to ensure adequate data protection.

TSIT may also use the information provided by or stored on the user purely for internal checks as regards demography, user interests and user behaviour. This use is carried out anonymised. TSIT may also statistically evaluate information on the user in an anonymised and aggregated form for advertising and market research. If and as far as TSIT GAMES uses user data to create user profiles, TSIT shall never pass on such profiles without the prior consent of the user and shall immediately stop such utilisation of user profiles if the user objects to such use of his data.

Only after their prior consent shall TSIT enable third parties to contact the user for advertising purposes. As long as the user does not object, his user data may also be used for sending the user advertising messages which reflect his interests (based on the information he has submitted to TSIT and on his actions within the websites and games operated by TSIT).

What other data do we collect and how are they used?

Your web browser or your client software transfers geographic data, information on your computer (e.g. performance data, gaming data processing, and type of browser) and data on the use of our products and services (e.g. time of login and logout). TSIT uses these data to create summary statistics of its community. Furthermore, TSIT can use these data for purposes of security and system integrity (e.g. to prevent hacking and cheating) or for purposes of prosecution. Please note that the use of your data may vary depending on the product and/or on the service.

Please check the documentation of your game. TSIT shall sometimes relate this information to your personal data, if TSIT is of the opinion that our Terms of Use have been infringed or if TSIT is ordered to do so by prosecuting authorities.

TSIT will also request you to enter a user name and a password. TSIT requests you not to use your real name, the name of another person or the name of a protected brand as a user name.

If you are a registered user, your details in TSIT databases can be stored to adjust the website to your specifications, to transmit user-specific information on TSIT, its partners or third-party providers or for other business purposes.

What are IP (internet protocol) addresses and how does TSIT use these?

An Internet Protocol ("IP")-address is a unique identification number assigned to your server or the server of your Internet service provider ("ISP"). TSIT ascertains IP-addresses in certain cases for purposes of system management, account authentication and system administration. TSIT might also use IP-addresses to restrict access to the servers of the company and to exclude individual systems so that the abuse of these servers is prevented.

TSIT might use these IP-addresses in connection with the data of a certain account or user if TSIT is of the opinion that our Terms of Use have been infringed or if TSIT GAMES is requested to do so by a judicial authority.

Disclosure to third parties

We treat your data strictly confidentially and do not disclose them to external third-parties.

However, TSIT might be legally obliged to disclose your data in individual cases, such as to investigating authorities, whereby data are then only disclosed as far as required by law.

TSIT shall engage subsidiaries or sister companies or third parties to provide services on our behalf in an individual case. This particularly applies to payment processing via external service providers (PayPal, Global Collect etc.). These external companies are obliged to treat your data confidentially, safely and in accordance with the law and May only use your data insofar as this is required to perform their task.

Amendments to or deletion of personal data

The user may change his personal data at any time (e.g. in order to update or correct such data) or delete his personal data completely. If the user would like TSIT to change his personal data or to stop using his data, the user may contact TSIT at info@tsitgames.com. TSIT will then make the required changes or delete the user data as quickly as possible.

However, TSIT points out to the user that for technical or organizational reasons, some measures may still be carried out after the user has submitted his request for deletion, if such measures had already been initiated but not completed by that time.

Information on personal data

Upon request, TSIT shall notify the user without delay of all personal data saved on him/her free of charge. This information will usually be provided electronically, normally by email.

TSIT reserves the right to amend this Privacy Policy at any time; however Kingsera GAMES shall always observe the respectively applicable laws on data protection. TSIT advises users to obtain information on the current Privacy Policy each time they visit websites and games. If TSIT would like to use the personal data of users to a greater extent than previously, TSIT shall, of course, notify users thereof in advance.

Should you have any general questions on this Privacy Policy and on data protection at TSIT GAMES, please do not hesitate to contact us at the addresses shown below. Please state your user ID, email address and, if appropriate, the game played. 

Data protection: info@tsitgames.com

Alternatively, you can send your enquiries to our postal address:

TSIT Games

Unit E5e Knoll business centre

Old Shoreham road

Hove BN3 7GS

UK

Information for parents

TSIT is well aware that we bear a special responsibility for personal data provided to us by children. Hence, TSIT recommends that parents tell their children never to actually enter their real names, addresses or telephone numbers without obtaining their parents' or their guardian's consent.

Children aged between 13 and 17 should ask their parents to read through these basic principles on personal rights and contact us if they would like to use the possibilities we have of restricting services or of voicing any concerns.

Minors under 18 may not register online for services subject to a charge without obtaining the prior consent of their parents or guardian. We kindly request parents and guardians to be particularly vigilant to ensure that their children do not break any laws while they use our websites or online services.

If you use services offered within the framework of the listed TSIT websites, you agree to the principles of TSIT concerning personal rights. If you do not agree to these principles, you should not use the services offered on these websites.

How safe are your personal data?

TSIT believes that it goes without saying that the data that you send us are protected and remain unchanged in their original form. Access to personal data is strictly monitored for this purpose. In addition, TSIT will do its utmost to ensure that subsidiaries and third-party providers, to whom TSIT might transfer your data, treat you with the same respect and focus on data security.

Third-party websites

Our websites might contain advertising or services which are linked to other websites, such as Twitter, Facebook and YouTube. The fact that TSIT creates a link to a website does not constitute any endorsement, approval or opinion concerning our relation to this third party. If you click on the link to the website of a third party - which includes advertisements - you leave the TSIT website you have accessed and change to the selected website. As TSIT GAMES has no control at all over the activities of third parties, we refuse to accept any responsibility whatsoever for the use of your personal data by such third parties. Furthermore, TSIT cannot guarantee that such third parties follow the same data protection and security practices as TSIT. You should therefore read through the data protection regulations of all other service providers whose services you use. Should you access the website of a third party which is linked to a TSIT website, you should first note the data protection regulations of this website before you disclose any personal information.

Products offered in cooperation with third parties

Users can register for other services from our website/websites. Certain products and/or services available on our website are offered to you in cooperation with third parties and might require that you state information serving to identify you, to register for those products and/or services and to ensure access to those products and/or services. Those products and/or services identify the third parties upon registration. If you register for those products and/or services the information serving to identify you is disclosed to those third parties and is subject to the data protection regulations and methods of those third parties. TSIT assumes no responsibility for the data protection regulations and methods of those third parties. For this reason, you should note the data protection regulations and methods of those third parties before you provide the information serving to identify you in connection with those products and/or services.

Glossary

To make this Privacy Policy easier to understand, the most important terms are briefly explained below:

What are personal data?

Personal data are data which identify the user. These data can be used to contact the user in reality or to locate him. These data include, for example, the user's correct name, email address, telephone number, postal address or credit card data.

What are user data?

User data are data which are collected, processed and stored by TSIT when a user contacts the websites and games operated by TSIT Co. Above all, user data are characteristics serving to identify the user (e.g. the domain name and/or the IP-address of the computer via which the user contacts TSIT), information on the start and end and on the scope of the respective use of the websites and games operated by TSIT and information on the accessed pages of the websites and games operated by TSIT.

Please note: If you make payment by credit card or PayPal in any of our websites we do not keep your card details, as this is all done via secure payment provider website or PayPal.

Last revised: 28/08/2013

All rights reserved to [TS Information Technology](http://www.tsit.org/) or [(TSIT Games)](http://www.tsitgames.com/)   
Unit E5e Knoll Business centre Hove BN3 7GS East Sussex UK
